(tape crackling)
(retro electronic music)
(sinister electronic music)
(water rustling)
(eerie electronic music)
(door clacking)
(water rustling)
(water trickling)
(ominous electronic music)
(curtain clanging)
(chilling atmospheric music)
(feet plopping)
(phone clacking)
(chilling atmospheric music)
- [Receiver] 911, what's your emergency?
- Hi,
could you send somebody over quickly, please?
(pensive atmospheric music)
I think there's an intruder in my house.
- [Receiver] Okay, ma'am,
I can send someone out to your area.
What's your address? - [Officer] Hello, police.
- Um, just a second.
(phone clacking)
(suspenseful electronic music)
- [Bob] Hi.
We're responding to some suspicious activity in the-
- Yeah, I called. I called.
- Are you here by yourself?
- Yes. Come in, come in.
- Great, great.
John, boy, what do you say we protect and serve?
(suspenseful electronic music)
- Hi. Thank you for sending them so quickly.
They, they just got here.
- [Receiver] Do not let them into your home.
We haven't sent anyone out to your area yet.
- What do you mean? They're already here.
(suspenseful electronic music)
(victim choking)
- [Receiver] Hello?
Ma'am, are you there?
(suspenseful electronic music)
(victim groaning)
What's happening? Hello?
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
Ma'am?
Hello?
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
Ma'am?
Hello?
(phone clacking)
- Five, six, seven, eight, and stretch.
(energetic electronic music)
And bounce.
(dancers clapping)
(energetic electronic music)
And turn.
(dancers clapping)
(energetic electronic music)
(upbeat electronic music)
(dancers clapping)
And stretch.
(upbeat electronic music)
Stretch
around.
(upbeat electronic music)
Around.
(Candy moaning)
(upbeat electronic music)
Bend it over, girls.
Whoo.
(upbeat electronic music)
(dancers clapping)
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Now stretch
those legs, ladies.
(upbeat electronic music)
Stretch again.
Oh, yeah.
(upbeat electronic music)
And again.
One more time, girls.
Oh, as big as you can.
Yes.
Now bend on over and stretch those hamstrings.
(upbeat electronic music)
Oh yeah.
So good.
(upbeat electronic music)
(menacing electronic music)
(Phoebe gasping)
- Oh my,
cut.
(Phoebe gasping)
Excuse me.
- [Candy] What is wrong with you?
- Cut? You don't get to say cut.
I say cut.
(Gino sighing)
- (chuckles) Phoebe, what the hell is the matter with you?
Everything was going beautiful.
- I'm uncomfortable with the choreography.
Candy is showing her nether regions to the camera.
- So?
- So? It's vulgar.
We're not making it porn, are we?
- Uh, eh...
(Gino sighing)
- Well, it makes me uncomfortable.
- This is what the audience wants, kid.
I mean they don't care about the exercises.
I mean, (chuckles), they just wanna wank the weasel,
pardon my French.
- Well, I care about fitness.
I care about the health of our children
and the obesity rate in our country.
We have a responsibility,
just like the president says.
- (sighs) Look, (coughs)
tell you what, kid, I promise you,
I will tell the cameraman to
go easy on the zoom lens, okay?
All right.
Now get on out there.
Hey, we're burning videotape here,
and that stuff ain't cheap.
(upbeat electronic music)
Get some more tight shots of the goodies, okay?
- Yes, sir.
- Get it?
Got it? Good.
(upbeat electronic music)
(Chuck groaning)
- Yo, Chiefy,
want me to get up there and fix these lights?
(upbeat electronic music)
- No, the lights are fine, Chuck.
- [Chuck] No, what I'm saying is I can make 'em better.
(upbeat electronic music)
- (sighs) We're good, man.
Trust me.
- Listen, I'm already putting on my gloves.
- Charles.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Okay. Okay, okay.
Coach, you make the plays, I back the plays you make,
okay?
(upbeat electronic music)
I'll get my ladder just in case.
- [Gloria] At first, Los Angeles police
thought the murder of a
female prostitute last month
was an isolated act of violence.
But since then, they've come to believe.
- God, I'm starving. - [Gloria] It was connected
to a series of assaults by a killer
who has become known as The Skid Row Strangler.
(package clattering)
- You want me to get you a soda from the vending machine?
- Um, maybe later.
- They have diet Mr. Pib?
- No.
- [Chuck] You sure?
- Yeah.
(crisp crunching)
- Whatever.
- Huh? - Chuck.
- Holy shit.
- (chuckles) Will you get me a soda
from the vending machine?
- You know my name?
(Candy chuckling)
Yeah.
Lucky for you,
I got a pocket full of change just for you.
I love you. I got you.
Get outta the way, fuck.
(upbeat electronic music)
(Chuck hitting wall)
(Nikki slurping)
- Nikki, what are you doing?
You can't eat fast food.
That cheeseburger is gonna make you slow and heavy.
- Don't worry about it.
I'll burn it off, okay?
I'm a stripper.
- Do they allow you to eat
burgers when you work the pole?
- Freddy, that is so degrading.
- [Monique] Hey, pole dancing does wonders.
I teach classes at Gold's on
Ventura, helps me stay in shape
for my wrestling matches.
- You're a wrestler?
- [Monique] Yeah. Oil, mud, jello, whatever.
Gino was one of the judges.
- What is this world coming to?
- Wanna see a move?
- [Phoebe] No, I don't.
I, I said no.
Oh, my God.
(Candy chuckling)
- Where did Gino get this square? (chuckles)
(members chuckling)
- For your information, Candy,
I got this job because Gino
noticed my leadership skills
while I was at work.
- Don't you work at that corn dog place at the mall?
Oh, I get it now.
Gino saw have you pumping up
and down making the lemonade
like, "Ah, ah, ah, oh, yeah, give it to me." (laughs)
- Maybe that's how you got this job.
- I am an actress, okay?
I am just doing this
because it's another stepping stone in my career.
That's why I'm on the cover.
(upbeat electronic music)
Thank you, dear.
- Mm-hmm, do you want a straw?
(upbeat electronic music)
- If you don't mind. - [Chuck] I don't mind at all.
- You know, this may just be another job to you guys,
but this means the world to me.
I wanna change lives.
(upbeat electronic music)
We're supposed to be role models.
(Nikki belching)
(members laughing)
- You've gotta be kidding.
- [Mikey] All right, ladies, (claps) come on.
Let's do it again.
(upbeat electronic music)
Come on, come on, come on.
Break time's over. Hustle, hustle.
(upbeat electronic music)
Make it look like you wanna be here.
All right, let's get sweaty.
(upbeat electronic music)
All right, roll camera
and action.
- Five, six, seven, eight, and stretch.
(upbeat electronic music)
And bounce.
- Gino.
- [Gino] Oh, Donna Stromboli. (groans)
- How ya doin', you little bastard. (laughs)
- Cut.
(Dominica groaning) (Gino groaning)
- [Gino] I want you to meet Dominica Stromboli.
Her and her husband are putting up the money
for this little video masterpiece.
Candy,
come here a minute.
This is Candy.
She's our cover girl. (chuckles)
Isn't she gorgeous?
And she's a real actress too.
What was the name of that picture of yours again?
- It's "The Co-ed Butcher."
- Oh. - Nice.
- That's it.
Oh, great picture.
Great picture.
- It's so nice to meet you, Mrs. Stromboli.
I really hope to meet Mr. Stromboli someday.
- Oh, you look like you're trouble to me.
(upbeat electronic music)
I'm keeping you away from my husband.
(Candy laughing)
Gino.
- Huh?
- Who's that hot, young stud over there?
- [Gino] Uh, that's Mikey,
uh, just outta film school.
- Maybe we should get him in some little shorts
doing some jumping jacks.
- Oh, I can have him do that for if you want, Dom.
He works for me.
- No, no, no. It's not necessary, let him work.
Can we have a moment, Gino?
- Oh, oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
Of course.
(mutters) In my office.
You guys,
take five
I's got to talk to the financier.
(upbeat electronic music)
(door clacking)
- We can eat.
(dancers chattering indistinctly)
(upbeat electronic music)
(Chuck sighing)
- Yo, Chief, I'm gonna pop up here
and fix these lights, okay?
- They're fine.
Okay, Chiefy, Jesus.
It's your show, man.
I'll do the dance.
You just gotta show me the moves.
(upbeat electronic music)
(Chuck grunting)
No?
Goddamn it, Jesus Christ.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Here you go.
Ah,
we are going to make a fortune with this video.
I mean what with all them girls spreading their legs
and showing off their
coochies and whatnot, (chuckles)
video's gonna fly off the shelf.
- That's great, Gino, my husband will be very pleased.
- Yeah.
- But you and I, we have an issue.
- An issue?
- [Dominica] It's my youngest, Isabella,
she needs something to focus on.
I wanna keep her away from
her low life street friends.
And I want you to put her in the exercise video.
- Oh. - Is that gonna be an issue?
- Oh, yeah.
No, no. Yeah, yeah.
No, of course. Yeah.
Oh, we'd be glad to have her.
I, I mean, (chuckles)
I can't wait to meet the young, broad, (coughs)
lady.
(menacing rock music)
Streets are a dangerous place
for a young lady nowadays.
All them perverts out there? (hisses)
No,
she'll be safe in here with me.
(menacing rock music)
(engine roaring)
(engine groaning)
(aggressive rock music)
(engine roaring)
(tires screeching)
(engine groaning)
(aggressive rock music)
(guitar screeching)
(gritty rock music)
(gritty rock music continues)
- Yo.
(menacing rock music)
- Can I help you?
- Yeah. Hold this.
(bag clanging)
(baggage clattering)
Thanks, babe.
- [Dominica] Oh, my baby girl.
(lips smacking)
Did you drive the Caddy here today?
- No. Daddy said I could take his car.
- Oh.
Okay.
- You two could be sisters.
It's,
it's uncanny. (chuckles)
- Isabella, this is Gino.
Gino is producing this workout video.
Don't you have something to say to him?
- (scoffs) Thank you, Gino, for this amazing opportunity.
And thank you, Mommy, for believing in me.
- Oh, isn't she a doll?
(lips smacking)
- Huh, she's, uh, gorgeous. - Eat you up. (laughs)
- Uh, Isabella, I,
why don't you go meet the rest of the crew, huh?
And then get changed.
We'll get started again in a few minutes.
- Okay. Bye, Mama.
- Bye, Sweetie.
- [Isabella] Love you. - [Dominica] Love you too.
- Eh.
Huh.
(upbeat electronic music)
(Mikey scoffing)
(Isabella sighing)
- Oh, thanks, babe.
- Yeah, no problem.
(upbeat electronic music)
- [Dominica] Now, don't let her give you any grief
and make sure she keeps her nose clean.
- Oh yeah. Yeah.
You got it, Dom.
I take care of her like she were my own little girl.
- Is there any place good to
eat around here? I'm famished.
- Try Papachinos.
Best Italian in the whole damn city.
I'll come with you. - [Dominica] No.
You have work to do.
And whatever you do, Gino,
do not let me down
because if you do,
you're gonna have to deal with Frankie.
(Gino gasping)
(upbeat electronic music)
(Gino chuckling)
I'm not joking.
- Okay.
- I'll be back.
(upbeat electronic music)
Let's go.
- Hi.
(Gino chuckling)
Hi.
(upbeat electronic music)
(Gino chocking)
Oh.
(Gino chuckling)
(Gino panting)
(door banging)
- Gino. How am I supposed to work like this?
There's another girl.
- Hey,
the lady putting up the dough
wants her kid in the video.
(hisses) That's it.
Just, just show her some moves. She'll catch on.
- But she's being a jerk.
- Look, I gotta get this thing shot, edited
and in the can and out to market in three days,
or it's my ass.
Now you begged me for this job,
so just use those leadership skills of yours.
- But this isn't the same as working at Hot Dog on a Stick.
All those girls out there are perverts,
strippers and communists.
- (scoffs) Look, kid,
this is not all about you,
remember that.
Now, (snuffles), I gotta take a minute
to go to the pawn shop.
There's this Arab guy still holding my watch.
You're in charge.
- But,
but they won't listen to me.
- Hey, take notes, kid.
This is how it's done.
(fingers snapping)
(members chattering indistinctly)
Listen up, you mooks.
Mrs. Stromboli is riding my ass,
so that means I'm riding your guys' asses, (hisses)
whatever.
Hey, you listen to Phoebe, huh?
She's in charge.
Now get this video done.
No more screwing around, capishe?
(Gino scoffing)
(metal clanging)
- Y'all wanna party?
- [Members] Yeah.
Whoo hoo.
- Can't have a party without tunes.
- [Member] Oh, yeah.
(members applauding)
(upbeat rock music)
- Director, get everyone under control,
- Relax, Phoebe.
Take five, or 10, or 30.
(upbeat rock music)
(Mikey coughing)
- So Isabella, is it true your dad's a mafia guy?
- He's in the sanitation business.
- So does that mean he's like a garbage man?
- He owns a few landfills.
I can give you a tour sometime.
- Ugh.
(upbeat rock music)
Hey, you guys
let's watch my scene from my movie.
(members applauding)
- You get naked?
- [Phoebe] Freddy, that's rude.
- Hell yeah,
in the first five minutes.
(upbeat rock music)
(tape clacking)
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Hello, this is Veronica.
Hi, Bobby.
What am I wearing?
(ominous atmospheric music)
I'm wearing a silky white teddy
and smooth white stockings.
(glass breaking)
(ominous atmospheric music)
Ugh.
Just a second, baby.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(phone clanging)
Sorry, baby,
I had to use the restroom.
(ominous atmospheric music)
Oh yeah. It was disgusting.
I totally blew it up.
Are you ready?
Are you ready to hear my shit?
Uh, (moans)
oh no.
(Veronica blowing)
(frightening atmospheric music)
(Veronica moaning)
(Veronica shrieking)
- [Members] Oh my God.
(members shrieking)
- [Nikki] Phoebe.
- [Monique] So annoying.
- You guys,
this is not appropriate viewing material for work.
We have a job to do.
- [Freddy] Get the hell outta the way, Phoebe.
- [Candy] This is my movie. This is my chance.
You need to move.
(members muttering indistinctly)
- [Candy] You're no fun and you're a loser.
- [Freddy] Bye bye. I hate you.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(victim muttering indistinctly)
- No.
No.
(groans) No, no.
(victim groaning)
(witness shrieking)
(blade screeching)
(ominous atmospheric music)
- No smoking, please.
- (chuckles) Are you talking to me?
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Oh. - What the fuck?
- I can't have you girls smoking pot.
I need you to be in top physical shape.
- You've got some balls, you know that?
Do you know who my father is?
I'll have you whacked like that.
- [Mikey] Okay. Okay, okay.
Nobody's whacking anybody.
(sighs) Phoebe, why don't you go outside and cool off?
- Me?
- Yeah, you're being a major buzzkill.
We're trying to watch a movie.
- [Freddy] Make yourself useful.
Go on a beer run. We're running low.
- Ugh, whatever.
(Mikey sighing)
- Sit, 'Bella.
- What the fuck are you doing in my house?
(blade screeching)
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Who are you?
(victim convulsing)
(victim chocking)
(victim muttering indistinctly)
Oh you've done this before, haven't you?
You're going to want to use two hands.
Okay, daddy.
(victim shrieking)
(wall banging)
(Isabella sighing)
(can opened)
- What's eating you?
- What's eating me?
I'm trying to get this video done.
And you show up and get everyone off track
with your delinquent ways.
- Yeah. My mom says that I have that effect on people.
- No, no, no.
- You son of a fucking bastard.
(victim muttering)
(blade shrieking)
(head smashed into rock)
(victim shrieking)
(blade clacking)
- Hey, hey.
(victim shrieking)
(blade shrieking)
- Hey, you're not allowed in here.
What are you doing?
Ah. (groans)
(blade shrieking)
(victim groaning)
- [Isabella] Look, I'm sorry.
I'm just trying to fit in.
- It's not like I can blame you.
They've been so horrible from the start.
No one respects me.
- I mean you're the boss, right?
They don't wanna listen to you,
persuade them.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Persuade them?
- Persuade them
real nice.
Smack 'em around a bit,
that's what my dad does.
- [Colleague] Where is Joey at?
He brings me all the way out here
and then he runs off doing God knows what.
(sighs) It's so cold out here.
(bones clacking)
(eerie atmospheric music)
(dark atmospheric music)
- Okay.
(Chuck muttering indistinctly)
(ominous atmospheric music)
- [Detective] What do we got, Doc?
- [Doctor] The victim's memory glands have been excised.
- [Detective] You mean?
- [Doctor] The guy cut her tits off
and took them with him?
(coughs) My God.
(coughs) Who would do something like that?
- [Doctor] A real sick fuck.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(sultry electronic music)
- Oh my God. Is this where you want me?
- Hell yeah. It's where I want you, Chuck.
- What's gonna happen now, dude?
- Horror movies make me
horny.
- Oh my God. Does that mean you're horny right now?
- Oh yeah. It does.
- Yeah.
- Can't you tell?
- I have no idea what horny looks like.
- Are you serious? You look like a stud.
- Oh my God. That's what my mom tells me too.
- Candy wants to party with Chuck.
And I wanna show you my party hats.
- Oh.
- Uh, you wanna party with Candy? (chuckles)
- Wait, we can't do this.
- No one's gonna catch us, dummy.
- Yeah, that's what they all say.
And the next thing you know, bam.
They're back to PA-ing.
I'm a filmmaker now, Candy.
I can't just go around sleeping with actresses.
- Ew.
Are you rejecting me? Have you seen my tits?
We were just watching them on the screen in there.
- Yeah,
in a movie,
the thing that I am gonna make
because I'm a filmmaker.
- No, you're not.
Why don't you just touch my
like everybody else does, Chuck?
- Yeah, well, maybe those people aren't about
to join the union Candy, but I am, okay?
- What kinda union?
I think that's fake. And I think you're making it up.
Look at my tits.
- Oh my God.
- Look at 'em, oh. - Put your boobs away.
- I would never put my boobs away.
- You're gonna put your boobs away.
- Oh yes. They're so warm.
Can't you just feel the heat coming off of them?
- Yes, I can.
But that's not the point.
If somebody comes in here right now and sees this,
I am never gonna get in the union.
- Look at them. - No.
- Everybody wants to look at 'em, Chuck.
- They're not gonna let me in the union.
- Oh yeah they will.
- No, they won't.
- They're soft. - No.
- And velvety. - Bet they are.
- And milky pale.
- Holy shit.
- And plump. - Wow.
You know what else is plump?
- What?
- Those fucking union paychecks.
- Oh, so what is this?
Are you seriously not gonna look at my tits?
- I'm so sorry. I'm sure your tits are really luscious.
- They're really, really good.
- I am not gonna ever look at your tits
until they're on a big screen
in a movie that I directed.
- Don't you wanna see these big, juicy melons?
- Nope.
- Are you on drugs?
Just put your hands on my tits like a normal
man.
- The only thing that's gonna
bang is the sound of a slate
when I'm making my movie.
Now get outta my office.
- Are you stupid, you fucking asshole?
Look at my tits,
look at 'em.
This is bullshit.
(Candy crying)
Look at my tits, ah.
(Candy wailing)
Please.
(door banging)
(Candy gasping)
She's my sister.
(door banging)
- Candy,
you are being very unprofessional
having sex and showing your dirty movies.
You need to get back to work, or else.
- (scoffs) Or else what?
What are you gonna do, you little twerp?
Are you gonna hit me?
You're just jealous of me 'cause I'm hot.
Do I make you uncomfortable?
Huh? (chuckles)
(Candy moaning)
Am I putting you in a weird position right now?
- Candy, please pull your shirt back down.
- You are a weirdo,
just look at them. - You're being
very unprofessional.
- Look at my tits, you fucking dummy.
- I will not look at your breasts.
- Oh no, you're gonna look at 'em.
- [Phoebe] No, I won't.
- Oh, absolutely you are,
'cause you're a little weirdo
and I've been noticing you looking at me anyways.
- Candy, this is so unprofessional.
- You haven't even seen unprofessional yet.
I'm gonna get really close to you until-
- Candy, stop.
- I'm gonna put all of my sweat on you, you fucking weirdo.
I paid for these tits
and somebody's gonna look at 'em
and it's gonna be you, you fucking bitch.
Look at my tits.
You're just jealous of me because I have tits!
- Stop.
- You don't wanna touch on this.
- Stop, stop, I don't wanna see. Stop.
- Look at 'em.
(Candy screaming)
(Phoebe shrieking)
(weapon shrieking)
Phoebe.
(Candy groaning)
(menacing atmospheric music)
(weapon clacking)
(doorknob croaking)
(door creaking)
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Holy fuck.
- I, I swear to God it wasn't me.
- Well, yeah. No shit.
This is like certified maniac shit right here.
(ominous atmospheric music)
Ugh God.
- What the hell are you doing just standing?
Holy jumping Jesus.
(scoffs) What the fuck happened?
- I don't-
- Candy.
Candy went to go get a drink
and we fucking found her like this.
- Oh, sweet baby Jesus.
Oh, Candy.
Oh, she didn't deserve that.
Yes, she, she was a nice piece of ass.
- Uh, do you think we should go to the cops?
- (scoffs) Like hell.
- Oh, okay.
- No, we ain't going to the cops.
Uh. Oh, help me, Jesus.
What the hell are we gonna do?
- Look. Look, look, look, look.
Just get rid of the body. That's what my daddy does.
- Ugh, God, your father.
- I can ask my mom for some help,
but you're gonna owe her big fucking time for this.
- Oh Christ.
(ominous atmospheric music)
Okay. Just make the call.
Phoebe. Go clean yourself up.
And nobody, nobody comes out here, you got it?
Get it? - Yeah.
- Good.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Come on.
- Oh. (sighs)
So we're all here, eh?
I (groans), I regret to inform you that Candy
has decided to walk off the project.
- What?
- [Nikki] What?
(ominous atmospheric music)
- So she just left?
Why?
- How should I know?
I didn't ask her no questions.
I don't know. Quit crawling up my ass.
- Oh, dude.
(ominous atmospheric music)
It has to be because I rejected her.
This always happens to me. Why am I so driven?
(ominous atmospheric music)
- So now what? Can we do it without Candy?
- (mutters) I, everybody, just, just sit tight
until I can talk to Mrs. Stromboli.
We'll get this all sorted out, okay? (chuckles)
(ominous atmospheric music)
(members whispering indistinctly)
- Hey, are you okay?
I know it's not easy seeing a dead body.
- You've seen a dead body before?
- [Isabella] Yeah.
In the streets, you see ODs, dead hookers,
bodies with their heads cut off.
Have you heard of the Skid Row strangler?
- No. Who's that?
- He's some sick fuck.
He likes to pretend he's a cop.
Strangles women, leaves 'em
for dead in the alley, naked.
Some sick fucking shit.
At least when my family wants to whack somebody,
it's just business.
- Just business?
Yeah, murder isn't supposed to be fun,
sometimes it's necessary.
Even the president knows that.
- Reagan?
- It's just business, baby.
- Yeah. Okay.
- I mean, somebody gets in your way,
you gotta take care of it.
(ominous atmospheric music)
Just business, baby.
- Yeah,
(ominous atmospheric music)
like Reagan says.
(body dragged on carpet)
(Gino mumbling)
(door creaking)
(Gino muttering)
- It's done, Mrs. Stromboli.
- [Dominica] Thank you, Frankie.
- (chuckles) Thank you.
Jesus I, (mutters)
Mr. Stromboli doesn't have to know about this, does he?
- He already does.
And he's not happy about it, believe me.
- Well, what are we gonna do, now?
Should, should we shut down the picture?
- Why? The situation has been handled.
I paid a lot of money for this video.
- But,
but there's a killer running around.
- Frankie did a sweep of the building.
There is no one here.
Unless, of course, one of your crew members is a killer.
- Well, no. No.
They, they were all in the studio
and except for Phoebe and Isabella.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- [Dominica] Lock all the doors.
Don't let anyone leave.
You have until midnight to finish this thing.
Don't make Frankie make two trips to the landfill.
Speaking of which, give him your keys.
(ominous atmospheric music)
You do have room in your trunk, don't you?
- Oh yeah.
Oh
Yeah.
Be careful with the interior.
I got payments.
- I'm gonna go freshen up.
Tell your director to find me in the office.
Come in here.
(door creaking)
(ominous atmospheric music)
- And the clutch sticks.
Oh.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(tumbler clanging)
- Gino, is the video canceled?
- No, we gotta keep going.
Oh, Jesus. Tits.
Now I gotta find a new cover girl.
(Phoebe gasping)
(suspense electronic music)
- Oh, Gino, please, please, please can I be the cover girl?
It was the role I was born to play.
Please, please, please, please.
- You?
- Yeah?
- Yeah, sure. Knock yourself out, kid.
- Oh Gino, thank you.
Thank you so much. You won't regret this.
I promise you. I will not let you down.
Thank you. Thank you.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Ugh, God. I need a goddamn drink.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much. I promise I'll never kill again.
I'll be good. I mean it.
Thank you, thank you. Thank you, thank you.
(upbeat electronic music)
Isabella, your thuggish ways have paid off.
You are looking at the new cover girl.
I can't believe this is happening to me. (chuckles)
- Well, that's pretty rad.
I guess it's good somebody killed her then, huh?
(upbeat electronic music)
- Yeah, I guess so.
- [Gino] All right, everybody get back to work.
Take it from the top.
- [Nikki] Um, who's going to take Candy's place?
- Me.
I'm the new cover girl.
- Why do you get to be cover girl?
- Because I have really great work ethic.
- [Nikki] Um we've been working just as hard as you.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Not to sound like a mega bitch,
but me, Monique and Nikki look the best, okay?
Call me mean, but it's the truth.
- Phoebe is a dud.
- She's a freak.
- Now all of you just shut up.
Please. Just shut up.
I'm sick and tired of all you broads
barking your demands at me.
Now I'm the boss.
(upbeat electronic music)
Now, you know,
I wanna see you ladies sweat a little.
So here's what we're gonna do.
Freddy's gonna take single shots of each of ya.
Whoever gives the best performance
gets the cover.
- I'll do it.
(upbeat electronic music)
(door opens)
(lively electronic music)
- No,
no, no.
I said no. Out, just get out.
(door banging)
Yeah, hey.
(hisses) My chihuahua looks better in tights.
And you broads,
you broads, just get back to work.
Jesus Christ.
Give me this, give me that.
Oh yeah.
Gino, give me the cover.
Well, blow me.
(menacing electronic music)
- Okay ladies, let's put our hair up.
Looks like we have a competition.
(menacing atmospheric music)
- [Nikki] Yes
we
Do.
- [Cassandra] You should probably
cut your losses now, Phoebe.
Candy may be gone, but you don't stand a chance.
Nikki is a stripper,
Monique's ripped, and (claps)
my ass is nicer than yours.
Hell, even mafia girl stands a chance.
Just accept your place and stay the back.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Just when I thought things were going my way,
these goddamn motherfucking cock sucking bitches
stage a coup.
Now I might not get the video cover
just because they're prettier than me.
It's not fair.
- Look, if you are as talented as you say you are,
you ain't got shit to worry about.
Or fight fire with fire.
(upbeat electronic music)
- I just don't wanna go against my values
any more than I already have.
(upbeat electronic music)
(Isabella chuckling)
- [Gino] Psst,
hey, Mikey,
come here a minute, huh?
(upbeat electronic music)
Mrs. Stromboli wants to talk with you in my office
to discuss
career options, huh?
Might be some financing for a film in it.
(Mikey chuckling)
- What about the video?
- Ah, Freddy can handle that.
(mutters) Now listen to me, Mikey,
youse got to do everything that she asks you to, eh?
Huh,
but by no means do you touch her.
Her husband is bad news.
(Gino shivering)
- But I have to do whatever she says?
- (groans) That's right.
- But don't touch her because I'll be dead?
- Exactly.
- But if I don't do what she says, I'm dead too?
- You got it.
Now, go on. Get in there.
Get it. (laughs)
(Gino smacking) - Oh.
- All right.
(upbeat electronic music)
- You uh,
you didn't tell her
that you're not exactly, uh, playing for her team?
(upbeat electronic music)
- I really wanna make a movie, Freddy.
- Welcome to Hollywood, bud.
(Freddy smacking)
(Mikey groaning)
(upbeat electronic music)
- So basically, I'm a filmmaker.
I mean I'm the one that sets the lights.
I set the mics, I build the sets.
I run the cable.
I mean, I do everything.
I'm making this movie really.
(upbeat electronic music)
I'm trying to join the union.
Did I already tell you that?
Yeah, I'm gonna join the union.
You should join the union.
- Chuck, I don't even think strippers have a union.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Well, you should.
They're super fucking cool.
(upbeat electronic music)
Wait, have you ever thought about being a roadie?
Dude, I have an extra set of fingerless gloves
you can borrow.
- Shut up.
(upbeat electronic music)
They're rad. You can still shred the guitar.
- Shut up.
- Wrap cable.
You can fucking do anything.
(upbeat electronic music)
- So, your mom let you to stay out late and stuff?
- [Isabella] I pretty much do what I want when I want.
Now close your eyes.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Isn't she afraid of you getting murdered
by the Skid Row strangler?
(upbeat electronic music)
- She's not that kind of mom.
One time I was staying with this punk band
for like a week or so,
she didn't even notice I was gone.
- You can tell she really loves you though.
She threatened Gino and
made him put you in this video.
That's love.
(can popping) - Yeah.
See, she thinks this thing's gonna like turn me around
and set me straight.
But I'm a lost cause.
- No, aerobics can do that.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Close your eyes.
(aerosol hissing)
(upbeat electronic music)
- Hey, I'll make a deal with you.
If you keep the camera on me at all times,
I'll go out with you.
- Oh, you can do better than that.
- Well, what do you want?
- Something special for my, you know, collection.
- Ugh, you pig.
(upbeat electronic music)
(ominous electronic music)
(vibrant electronic music)
(exciting electronic music)
- Um, Isabella, I don't know if I can do this.
- [Isabella] Sure you can.
You just need to loosen up a little bit.
You wanna do some blow?
- What? No, I cannot.
I don't do drugs. No.
What would President Reagan think?
- Reagan will be just fine. Trust me.
(upbeat electronic music)
- (chuckles) I don't know.
Even Nancy?
(upbeat electronic music)
- Nancy's gonna be just fine as well.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- Okay, if you say so.
(Phoebe snorting)
(Phoebe coughing)
Oh God.
- [Isabella] Yeah, let's uh.
(Phoebe gasping)
Yeah, I'm gonna take that.
- Okay. Thank you.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Yeah, we're gonna, um,
you'll be fine.
- Yeah? - It's gonna be great.
Yeah, it's gonna be great.
It's gonna be great. - Reagan doesn't care.
- [Isabella] Yeah.
- No. (chuckles) - [Isabella] No, Reagan,
Reagan doesn't care, you're good.
- Okay.
Okay.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(doorsill clanging)
You, Monique.
(upbeat electronic music)
Hey you. Monique.
Can I speak to you over here?
- Yeah, what is it?
(upbeat electronic music)
(door clanging)
- All right, come on.
Come in, follow me, come on.
Faster, come on.
Private conversation, shut
the door behind you, please.
Private.
(door banging) I've just been thinking a lot
about symmetry.
Do you think symmetry is important?
'Cause I think symmetry is very important.
I think we need one less girl.
So I think you should leave.
- Ugh, that's bullshit.
You can't make that call. You're not the boss.
- (snuffles) Mm, actually,
I remember when Gino put me in charge.
Do you remember that? 'Cause
I remember that pretty well.
Do you remember that?
Well, I'm just thinking about the video.
I have the video first in my head, you know?
I think it's the most important thing, the video.
I think the video should come first.
I think it should come first.
Do you think it should come first?
'Cause I think the video should come first
and I think you should leave.
- Why me? Why not the mafia girl or Cassandra or Nikki?
I'm the most physically fit.
- [Phoebe] Um, well, you know,
I'm not a big fan of those girls either.
But I'm also really not a big fan of wrestling.
I think, you know,
aerobics is much harder than wrestling and-
- Wrestling requires way
more strength than aerobics.
You're just discriminating 'cause I'm a wrestler.
- Ha.
First of all, no, because, you know, it's just business.
It's not personal. It's just business, so no.
Also, second of all, no.
Wrestling is not harder than aerobics.
- (sighs) Really?
You wouldn't last a second with me, Pho-bee.
(Phoebe laughing)
- You wanna try me?
- Yeah.
- No, no.
Hey, Monique, stop it. Stop it.
Okay, wrestling is cool.
(menacing rock music)
(Phoebe muttering indistinctly)
You're going to kill me.
(Monique groaning)
(menacing rock music)
Stop it.
(bone cracking) (Monique shrieking)
(Monique shrieking)
(menacing rock music)
(Monique choking)
(Phoebe groaning)
(bone cracking)
(chair clanging)
(gritty rock music)
I'm sorry, Monique,
it was for the greater good.
♪ You ♪
- My name is Phoebe.
(upbeat electronic music)
Whoo, come on, let's get started. Come on, whoo.
- Where's Monique?
- (claps) I had to let her go.
- Why?
- [Phoebe] For aesthetic reasons.
Do you wanna be next? Get in line.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Who died and made you leader?
- Candy did, bitch. (chuckles)
(upbeat electronic music)
Ready? Five, six, seven, eight.
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo.
(upbeat electronic music)
(upbeat electronic music continues)
(lively electronic music)
- [Freddy] Okay, it looks like we got the shot.
- Oh, thank you, Jesus.
All right,
now get the solo shots and
then get to editing immediately.
- So who's gonna be on the cover?
- [Gino] Look, I don't know the answer to that.
You want the answer to that?
You'll have to wait till it's done.
All you broads clear out, huh?
(chuckles) Mikey's got a meeting he's gotta go to.
(door banging)
- So who wants to shoot first?
- I'll go first.
- Awesome.
(gentle electronic music)
(energetic electronic music)
- Well, hello there.
- Hi, Mrs. Stromboli.
Gino said you wanted to see me.
- Please, call me Dominica.
(energetic electronic music)
Come in. Step into my office.
(lively electronic music)
Shut the door.
(door closing)
Come sit next to me.
(lively electronic music)
- [Mikey] Um, on the table?
- Yeah, right here.
(Mikey muttering) -Have a seat.
- Okay.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Let's talk about your career,
Mikey.
(bottle clanging)
(cork popping) - Oh.
(Dominica moaning)
(upbeat electronic music)
- Would you settle down?
You're starting to give me fucking motion sickness.
What's your fucking problem?
- I just wanna know what she's doing in there.
- She's probably blowing him.
- That's prostitution.
- (claps) That's America, sweetie.
- (gasps) That's not Reagan's America.
(menacing rock music)
- Some people have to do it to survive.
(upbeat electronic music)
They gotta do what they gotta do.
I like to do it for the thrill.
(upbeat electronic music)
- You know, I don't understand you.
You have a mom that loves you so much,
a dad that lets you drive his super-cool cars
and you go out and turn tricks on the street for fun?
What the heck is wrong with you?
(upbeat electronic music)
Well, sorry I wasn't born with the perfect mom and dad
like you were.
- (gasps) You know nothing about my life.
- [Dominica] Tell me, what do you see for yourself?
- [Mikey] Well, I would like to be a filmmaker
and make feature films.
I have some ideas.
- Mm,
you are so creative.
(upbeat electronic music)
How would you feel about
going into business together?
- Uh,
yeah, that would be awesome.
Um, I mean
I, I would like to have a meeting with you
and your husband.
(gentle electronic music)
- We need to get really close, Mikey.
We need to build a relationship.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Okay.
That's your tongue.
(tongues slurping)
(Dominica moaning)
- I just wanna know why you and not me?
Why does someone like you get all the breaks?
And you don't even care.
(Isabella sighing)
(sighs) It just makes me so mad.
(upbeat electronic music)
- What are you gonna do? Kill me like Candy and Monique?
I'm not a snitch, okay?
At least that's one good thing
my parents could teach me.
But what you should know,
you can't kill your way to the fucking top, okay?
People need to like you.
Yeah, my mom and dad are criminals,
but at least people love them.
(upbeat electronic music)
(menacing rock music)
(Cassandra smacks butt)
- [Reporter] We interrupt this broadcast
to bring you an important news break.
The body of a young woman was found
near a construction site by the Ventura Freeway
early this morning.
Authorities are asking citizens
not to travel alone at night
or accept rides from strangers.
We will bring you more
information as this story develops.
(menacing rock music)
- Show's over.
- That's it?
We just started.
(menacing rock music)
(upbeat electronic music)
- Mrs. Stromboli, we can't be doing this.
You're a married woman.
- Oh, don't you worry about that.
He's got his little whores on the side.
And if he can play,
I can play.
- Oh, so this is okay with him?
- Oh God, no.
If he finds out, he'll cut your dick off
and shove it down your throat.
- Oh my God. Oh, you're strong, Mrs. Stromboli.
- You don't have to worry about that.
We're just talking.
(bangles clattering)
- Little rat skin.
- I am being the perfect,
loyal,
(jewelry clattering)
(gentle electronic music)
loving
wife.
(gentle electronic music)
Do you want me to tell him
that you couldn't keep your hands off of me?
(gentle electronic music)
- (sighs) No, ma'am.
(door creaking)
- Hi, Freddy.
I'm ready for my solo shoot if you are.
- Oh rad. Let's get started.
(eerie atmospheric music)
- So how's the footage looking?
- Good, you know?
Real hot, you know?
But I know that's not the reason why you're asking.
- What do you mean?
- You don't have to play coy.
I know all you ladies wanna be on the cover.
- I just want the best girl to win.
And I believe the best girl is me.
- Yeah. How are you gonna prove it?
(eerie atmospheric music)
- Miss Stromboli.
(sultry atmospheric music)
(Dominica laughing)
- Like that, don't you?
You're an animal.
Oh, baby.
(Mikey muttering indistinctly)
- So what do you say, Phoebs?
How bad do you want this cover?
Enough to give me a private show?
- Why is everyone in this city such a goddamn scumbag?
I'm gonna report you to Gino.
- (chuckles) He doesn't care.
All he cares about his leg doesn't get broken
by some gombas.
So are you gonna show me?
(ominous atmospheric music)
(Freddy groaning)
(Cassandra shrieking)
- I knew it. You're busted.
Wait till I tell everyone.
- Cassandra, don't, please. - Oh my God.
- No.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Help.
Help please.
Stop.
Please stop.
(engine rumbling)
Help.
(ominous atmospheric music)
Officer, please help.
She killed Freddy.
Phoebe killed Freddy.
Thank God you guys are here.
- Yeah, thank God.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Oh, Isabella, oh my God.
I'm so sorry. You have to help me.
The cops are coming. I killed Freddy.
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- Oh, I don't know.
I just like wanted everything to be fair.
And then like, I know, he just made me really, really mad
and I just had to kill him.
But then the cops are here, I'm sorry.
- Oh my fucking God.
I can't keep cleaning up your goddamn messes.
Get the fuck outta here.
- Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
(shoes clacking)
- It's okay, baby. I'm here to protect you.
Well, why don't you get in my car?
- No, we have to go back to the studio.
The other girls are in danger. (sobs)
- Other girls?
(ominous atmospheric music)
What did we do to deserve this?
(officer laughing)
- We're gonna make detective tonight.
- Whoo
(ominous atmospheric music)
- [Mikey] I think I heard a noise.
Okay, that's for the money. That's for the fame.
Oh, she's biting it.
You're biting real hard, Mrs. Stromboli.
What's your favorite mountain bike up here?
Okay.
- [Dominica] Shut up. - Camera.
(Mikey and Dominica moaning)
My own star on the Walk of Fame.
(sultry atmospheric music)
Lights,
camera.
(Mikey muttering)
Want some action?
(Dominica laughing)
(sultry atmospheric music)
(ominous electronic music)
- Oh, bogus, dude. That's not cool.
- There has to be an explanation for this.
- Yeah. Phoebe's a fucking lunatic.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- [Gino] Holy Christ!
How is it you kids keep getting
yourself brutally murdered?
- Phoebe killed Freddy, I saw her.
I told the cops.
(Gino gasping)
- You told the cops?
Why the fuck you do that?
- Why are you yelling at me?
- Look, she's a fucking idiot, okay?
We gotta do something now.
- [Chuck] Hey, you got a problem with the fuzz, boss?
(ominous atmospheric music)
I can dig it.
Let's just say there's a little bar down in Houston
that I can't step foot in for reasons.
- Well, we gotta get rid of them, that's for sure.
I got it.
- I'll start an electrical fire.
We'll burn the whole building
down. Everyone will evacuate.
It'll get rid of the evidence.
I'll make it look like an accident. I've done it before.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- I like the way this guy fucking thinks.
- Are you fucking insane?
We ain't gonna burn the place down.
- Okay.
Okay. All right, it's your hoedown, man.
You just tell me when to allemande or dosey doe.
- We gotta act fucking fast, Gino.
- [Gino] Well, okay, wait.
(gaps) I'm just gonna have to put on a charm. That's all.
Yeah, that's it.
Uh, let me do all the talking, all right?
Okay? You got it?
Get it? Good.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Okay.
- We need to do something. You need to go find Phoebe.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- You think she's good for this?
- No, not really.
But go find Phoebe. Make sure she's safe.
I'll take care of the fucking cops, okay?
(ominous atmospheric music)
- No, I'll pretend I'm a homicidal maniac.
I'll put on a hockey mask and I'll get a chainsaw,
and I'll fucking scare 'em away.
- They're gonna fucking shoot you.
- They never shoot the killer in the movies.
- It's the LAPD, are you fucking kidding me?
They shoot everybody.
Look, I need you to go find Phoebe.
Make sure she's safe, cause a fucking distraction,
I'll take care of the rest.
- Okay.
All right. You got it, boss.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- [Dominica] Oh my God. - [Mikey] Oh,
oh my God.
(Mikey muttering)
My glasses.
- Fuck your glasses. I want you to fuck me. (groans)
(sultry atmospheric music)
- And I'm gonna get money for the film, right?
Yes you are, baby.
(door thudding)
(gasps) What was that?
- I didn't hear anything.
(door banging)
- [Officer] Police, open up.
- Oh fuck.
Put your clothes on, dummy.
Good evening, officers.
How can I help you?
- [John] Can you get off the table, please.
- Officers, I'm sure we can discuss this.
- I said
stand the fuck up.
- Can I at least put my shirt on?
- Get off the table.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Do you know who I am?
- I don't give a shit who you are.
Now up against the table.
(ominous atmospheric music)
Spread 'em.
- [Dominica] Hey.
- Get your hands off.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- What did you say to me, boy?
- Just be gentle, okay?
(firearm clacking)
Looks like we got ourselves a hero here, John.
- Calm down, Bob.
We still got a killer to find.
You two,
main room.
Come on. Go.
Go on. Main room.
Wear a shirt, don't wear a shirt. Nobody gives a shit.
Fucking ruining my fun, John.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- There's gotta be something.
Oh.
(door opening)
Oh, baby.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Get the fuck off my mom, you fucking asshole.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
What the fuck?
- It's okay, baby. I'm fine.
- [John] Oh Bob.
Looks like we got us a mother-daughter team here.
- [Isabella] What the fuck's wrong with you?
(Bob laughing)
- I ain't never done a mother and a daughter
at the same time before, it could be fun.
(Gino chuckling)
- [Gino] (groans) Good evening, officer.
I'm Gino Antonioni,
I am the owner of this studio.
So is there a problem here?
- [John] Well, Mr. Antonioni,
I have it from sugar tits here
that there's been a murder on the premises.
You wouldn't know anything about that?
- Oh, she's delirious.
She's been up all night exercising.
It's working out. Sweating.
No hey, she's on drugs.
- [Cassandra] I'm not high.
I saw Freddy with my own eyes.
- Cassandra, please.
- [Cassandra] No, you're hiding the truth.
- Is there anyone else in the building?
- [Gino] No. This, this is, this is it, yeah.
- Well, I'll tell you what's gonna happen.
Me and this little Miss Thing
are gonna go find a private room
and I'm gonna interrogate her properly.
- Cassandra, don't.
- Hey, you sit still, goddamn it.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- [John] The rest of you can get to know my partner, Bob.
Walk.
- Yes, officer.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(Gino muttering)
(eerie atmospheric music)
(door creaking)
- [John] All right, sweet cheeks,
park it here.
Tell me what you saw.
- You hiding something
underneath that dress of yours?
I think I'm gonna have to pat you down again.
- Hey, man. Cool it.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Handcuff yourself to the railing of that door
now.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(handcuffs clattering)
Now.
- Hey, just do what he says, Mikey.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(handcuffs clattering)
(Bob laughing)
- That's a good boy.
- [Mikey] Huh.
- Just do what we say and we'll let you go.
What's he doing to Cassandra?
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Interrogate her.
Right about now,
he's interrogating her real good.
(Bob chuckling)
(ominous atmospheric music)
- [Cassandra] I knew that girl was a head case
from the moment I met her.
She's mega disturbed.
- Uh huh.
- She tried telling us what to do,
and we told her to get bent and she turned psycho.
The rest of the crew is shady too.
The Latina girl is a stripper.
The Italian girl and her mom,
they're gangsters.
I believe Gino has a warrant out.
- Oh.
(Cassandra coughing)
(head banging)
(ominous atmospheric music)
(John coughing)
(John groaning)
Oh fuck, that was a good one.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(belt clacking)
(John chuckling)
(John groaning)
(John sighing)
(John laughing)
Oh fuck.
(floor creaking)
(gasps) What?
(ominous atmospheric music)
Was that you?
The one they've been looking for.
They say you killed somebody.
Is that right? (chuckles)
(ominous atmospheric music)
No.
No. I'm not gonna hurt you.
I like you.
We both hate stupid girls,
who don't know how to listen.
Who's laughing now, huh?
Tell you what, I'll make you a deal.
You stay right there, right where you're hiding,
and we'll let you go. (laughs)
I can tell you're a smart cookie, just
please,
(ominous atmospheric music)
don't do anything stupid.
(door creaking)
(door banging)
(ominous atmospheric music)
Oh.
- [Bob] Did she squeal?
- Oh, like a pig.
- [Mikey] Where's Cassandra?
What did you do to her?
(bottle banging)
She is being held for more questioning.
Now the real question is who do I
interrogate next?
How about you?
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Well, I didn't do, I didn't see anything.
- [John] Well, according to
the other little lady in there,
you're a dancer.
I'd like to corroborate that.
- I didn't do anything.
Really, I'm not a dancer. I don't know how to dance.
What is dancing?
- (sighs) Just do what he says.
- [John] Let's see it.
- Okay.
(upbeat electronic music)
- How about some flash dancing?
On the chair.
- Okay.
(upbeat electronic music)
(chair clattering)
(sultry electronic music)
- It's time for the big finish.
(Bob shouting)
(Nikki coughing) Yeah.
(John laughing)
(sultry electronic music)
- [Bob] Take it off, baby.
No, no, no, no.
The shoes.
Keep the top on.
(sultry electronic music)
Keep going.
Socks.
(sultry electronic music)
Let's go.
- [John] Ooh.
Come on, Bob.
Get in there and do some real detective work for once.
(sultry electronic music)
Are you ticklish?
- No.No.
(sultry electronic music)
- Think we can make her ticklish?
- [John] I know you can, Bob.
(sultry electronic music)
(lips smacking)
- Okay, officer.
I think we've cooperated here quite enough.
I must say though, your methods are a little queer.
- [John] Queer?
You calling me queer?
I ain't no fucking queer.
(Gino sighing)
The ladies can't keep their hands off me. Ask Bob.
- [Bob] He's all man.
(body thudding)
(chair clattering)
- Yeah.
I bet you guys like to see each other in action, huh?
How about you both get the fuck outta here
and go fuck each other up the ass.
I bet that's what you both really want, huh?
- I love that filthy little mouth.
You just became
my number one suspect. - Don't you touch my baby,
you son up a bitch.
- [John] Yeah, Bob, we got us a mother-daughter team here.
Can't split that up.
Think it's only fair we interrogate them together.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Who gets who? I want the one with the filthy mouth.
- Well, shit. I want a turn.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- [Dominica] Take me.
I'll do anything.
(ominous atmospheric music)
I know what a man like you wants.
I know how to please a man like you.
I'll let you do anything.
You can slap me, you can cut me
and I will cry and I will scream for you.
(ominous atmospheric music)
(John chuckling)
(sinister atmospheric music)
- You know, I don't usually go for broads your age.
I don't even go for broads your daughter's age.
(ominous atmospheric music)
I like them much, much younger.
But I don't know,
(ominous atmospheric music)
you're really doing something for me.
Hold this, come on.
- Ma. No, don't.
(Bob laughing)
- [Dominica] It's okay, baby.
- Gotcha.
- [Dominica] I've been through this before.
- Get the fuck off me, you fucking cock sucker.
- Keep talking filthy, it's getting me all excited.
(ominous atmospheric music)
- Ma.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Phoebs,
where are you going?
- I've gotta get outta here.
- I can't let you do that.
(upbeat electronic music)
Isabella, she sent me to come find you,
make sure you're okay.
- She said that?
- Fuck yeah she did.
- Oh. - Listen,
people said you did some super gnarly shit in there,
but you still got friends.
Whatever it is, we can work through it.
We're film family.
- You're right. I can't leave now.
- Yeah.
Hey, you know what?
Chill here.
I gotta cause a distraction
to get rid of those fucking cops.
- Wait, they're not cops.
- Tho, those guys are bad.
I'm gonna go back in there. You make that distraction.
I'm taking your hammer.
(shoes clacking)
(upbeat electronic music)
- All right,
whatever, dude.
Let's go.
(equipment clattering)
(Dominica shrieking)
(upbeat electronic music)
- Come here.
(John sighing)
(upbeat electronic music)
(John groaning) (Dominica chuckling)
(punch) (Dominica shrieking)
(ominous atmospheric music)
(Isabella groaning) (Bob laughing)
- Get off of her, you ugly fuck.
(handcuffs clattering)
- Oh, Jesus Christ,
you shouldn't be doing that.
- Yeah. Why's that?
(ominous atmospheric music)
(Bob chuckling)
(hammer hitting Bob)
(lively electronic music)
(Dominica shrieking)
- Goddamn it, Bob,
can you keep them quiet for five fucking minutes?
(lively electronic music)
(handcuffs clattering)
- You need to get outta here.
- I'm not leaving here without my mom.
(handcuffs clattering)
(Dominica shrieking)
(Dominica panting)
- [John] You know what?
This isn't working for me.
(handcuffs clattering)
You're too fucking
(Dominica sobbing)
womanly.
I'm gonna come back in about five minutes
and I'm just gonna kill you. (chuckles)
See you soon.
(Dominica sobbing)
(shoes pattering)
Goddamn it, Bob. Get up.
Get up.
- (shrieks) God, what the fuck happened?
- They went for the,
they went to get the fucking mother.
- Goddamn.
(suspenseful electronic music)
- Son of a bitch.
(John groaning)
(John groaning) (Mikey groaning)
(suspenseful electronic music)
- Hey, fuck-face.
- What?
(gun shot)
(John groaning)
God
damn it.
(Gino laughing) (John writhing)
(John groaning)
God,
you shot me in the fucking ear.
(John groaning)
- Sorry, kid.
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
(door clattering)
(John groaning)
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
- [Isabella] Ma.
The fuck did that fucker do to you?
- [Dominica] I'm fine, baby.
Just, just unlock me.
- Jesus, guys come on.
Would you, would you hurry up?
(panels clattering)
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
- You little shit.
(Phoebe chocking)
(suspenseful electronic music)
(Phoebe groaning)
(hammer hitting head)
(blood spit out)
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
(hammer pulled back from head)
(door clattering)
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
- Help.
(stab sound)
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
- You like that?
(organs screeching)
(suspenseful atmospheric music)
(Nikki groaning)
(guts falling)
(Nikki choking on blood)
(body thudding)
(suspenseful electronic music)
- [Phoebe] Mikey.
- Oh, I think my ribs are broken.
- Ooh, really? (Mikey shrieking)
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Why would you do that?
- I don't know. I'm uh, I'm sorry.
It's okay. Let's get you outta here.
- No, just go.
The other one's still in the building.
- What?
(Phoebe shrieking)
- Phoebe.
(Mikey groaning)
- No. No.
- When I asked you not to do anything stupid,
this is exactly what I was talking about.
(Phoebe cries out)
Now, where is that goddamn mother
and her whore of a daughter?
(suspenseful electronic music)
- I'm not a snitch.
(Phoebe slapped) (Phoebe shrieking)
- Useless!
(suspenseful electronic music)
(Dominica gasping)
- Oh.
(suspenseful electronic music)
(Dominica shrieking)
- What the fuck?
(Dominica shrieking) Get the fuck off of her.
Get off my mom.
(Isabella shrieking)
Goddamn it.
- What the fuck is this?
(chainsaw roaring)
Who the fuck are you?
- You better leave, man.
I'm gonna cut,
I'm gonna cut you real bad.
(chainsaw dies)
- Oh. Oh, you're gonna cut me?
You're gonna fucking cut me?
- I'm just messing around, man.
I'm just messing around.
Chill, man. Chill.
- Who the fuck you think you're dealing with?
(ominous atmospheric music)
You think this is a movie?
No.
I'm the real fucking deal.
(chainsaw roaring) (John groaning)
(dagger clattering)
(chainsaw roaring)
(severed fingers hitting ground)
(menacing rock music)
♪ Yeah ♪
- [John] Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You, you don't have to do this.
You, you and me. We're the same.
I, I don't want to kill.
I have to kill, just like you.
- We are not the same.
- Sure we are.
We, we both hate stupid girls.
I, I know you're not.
You're a smart girl, and what I'm gonna do,
I'm gonna get in my car,
I'm gonna drive away and you'll never see me again.
You, you, you already got Bob.
You killed Bob. You don't need revenge.
You, you have nothing to gain from this.
- This isn't about revenge. This isn't personal.
This is just business.
(chainsaw roaring) (menacing rock music)
♪ You can feel the burn. Murdercise. ♪
(chainsaw roaring)
♪ Murdercise. You can feel the burn ♪
♪ Murdercise. Murdercise ♪
♪ You can feel the burn. Murdercise. ♪
♪ Murdercise. She's lost in her joy joy ♪
♪ Joy. All her joy ♪
(chainsaw roaring)
♪ Too much joy. ♪
(foot stomping on head)
(Phoebe panting)
(upbeat electronic music)
(Dominica coughing)
- Oh, Don,
thank God you are safe.
I prayed to Mary, Joseph and Jesus.
Oh, thank God you're safe.
- Thanks for nothing.
You left us all here to die, you putz.
- No, I, I went for help.
- Yeah. Yeah.
You are useless.
- Mikey.
- Phoebe.
Careful.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Where are these bastards?
- (sighs) I'm okay, Frankie,
and they're all dead.
Phoebe got em.
(upbeat electronic music)
(Gino sighing)
- [Gino] Well, hey, nice job, kids.
Especially you, Phoebe.
Uh, I mean, saving Mrs. Stromboli,
you saved all our asses, huh?
- (sighs) What can I say?
- [Gino] And you, Mikey, (chuckles)
there's a gold watch in this for you,
slightly used and later,
but a gold watch.
- Congratulations.
- [Mikey] Thanks, Gino.
- (sighs) I guess it's back to Hot Dog on a Stick for me.
- [Gino] Oh, no, no, no.
I promise, the next video, even better.
- [Dominica] There's still the matter of this video, Gino.
You are still on the clock.
- But,
but there's bodies all over the place.
- Well, you've got your work cut out of you now don't you?
Get rid of the bodies.
Oh, and Phoebe will be the next cover girl.
- Oh. (gasps)
I don't know what to say, Mrs. Stromboli.
Thank you so much. (gasps)
- How would you like to join our family, Phoebe?
(upbeat electronic music)
- Boy, I'd love to.
- And Isabella here,
I'm sure would love to have you around more. (chuckles)
- Really? You mean that, Isabella?
- Yeah. I guess,
having a level-headed homicidal maniac as a friend,
it'd be all right.
- Ms. Stromboli,
it would be an honor.
- Call me Ma.
And Mikey,
you are going to need a nurse
and I will personally make sure that you heal
and recover.
- Oh, ribs. Ribs.
(Phoebe groaning)
Ribs. - Oh, right, sorry.
(video tape starts)
♪ O say can you see ♪
- Hi, I'm Phoebe Wrenkowski,
and I have a message for the youth of today.
Crack is whack.
Say no to drugs, say no to communism
and always practice safe sex
by not doing it.
Build a better body and we
could build a better America.
♪ Through the perilous fight ♪
♪ O'er the ramparts we watched, ♪
♪ were so gallantly streaming ♪
♪ And the ♪
(menacing rock music)
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ She's just an innocent girl ♪
♪ And she's lost in the shadows of her world ♪
(menacing rock music)
♪ And she's just doing what's told ♪
♪ She looks out the window and it's so cold, cold, cold ♪
♪ It's so cold ♪
(menacing rock music)
♪ Whoa, ho, ho ♪
♪ The window knows ♪
(menacing rock music)
♪ You can feel the burn ♪
♪ Murdercise, pain is gain ♪
♪ She's lost her innocence boys ♪
♪ And now life is her toy ♪
(menacing rock music)
♪ She's lost in renaissance boy ♪
♪ She's lost in her joy, joy, joy ♪
♪ All the joy ♪
(menacing rock music)
♪ Whoa, ho, ho ♪
♪ Too much joy ♪
(menacing rock music)
♪ You can feel the burn ♪
♪ Murdercise, pain is gain ♪
- [Phoebe] No one respects me.
(menacing rock music)
- [Isabella] I mean you're the boss, right?
They don't wanna listen to you?
Persuade them.
(gritty rock music)
- [Phoebe] Persuade them?
- [Isabella] Persuade them.
(gritty rock music)
Real nice.
Smack 'em around a bit.
(gritty rock music)
That's what my dad does.
(upbeat rock music)
The murder isn't supposed to be fun,
sometimes it's necessary.
(upbeat rock music)
(upbeat rock music continues)
(retro electronic music)
(retro electronic music continues)